

NURUL FAJRI

Full-stack Developer

phone: +62 878 3755 4403 email: n.fajri@outlook.com

I have been interested in Software Development since 2017, so my hobby is exploring new things related to technology. I have over 4 years of experience in software development and junior in web3 development. I am a person who quickly adapts to new things, can work in a team, is solution-oriented and has good stress management when there are work-related problems.

I'm currently developing a lot of boilerplate/starter applications on the frontend and backend whose repositories are Open Source and under MIT license. It can be accessed at https://github.com/masb0ymas.

My CV can also be seen on the following website: https://www.masb0ymas.my.id

The following is a summary of my educational history, work experience, project portfolio and technical abilities.

Experience

57

Software Engineer

Moneyflow ID - Self-employed June 2023 - Present Jakarta, Indonesia

My first internet product with a subscription type, this application only focuses on cash flow, both from recording income, expenses, budgeting and reporting every month. This application is equipped with a feature to scan grocery receipts and find out your income or expenses.



Software Engineer

Trasmi Broker - Full-time August 2022 - Present Jakarta, Indonesia - Hybrid

I rebuilt the insurance broker system from scratch again, because the old system could not be maintained well. The broker system that I created only helps brokers in cross checking data from bank to insurance and vice versa.



Software Engineer

Karcisbola - Full-time

April 2021 - November 2023 Jakarta, Indonesia

I built a ticketing & raffle system from scratch on the Karcisbola application, including a payment gateway, but the ticketing system is not yet fully used. I also researched many clouds to reduce costs in terms of deployment, both staging and production.



Nusantech

Full-time

Full-stack Developer

September 2020 - April 2021

The first time I worked at this company, I played the role of Backend Developer, this company operates in the Software House sector for private and government companies. with the many applications created, I developed many skills learned, both from the Backend, Frontend and DevOps side.

Web Developer

June 2019 - September 2020

The first time I worked at this company, I played the role of Backend Developer, this company operates in the Software House sector for private and government companies.

Education



Universitas Putra Indonesia "YPTK" Padang

Bachelor of Computer Science

April 2013 - March 2017

Technical Ability

Programming Language

- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Go
- PHP
- Dart
- Solidity

Experimental

- Microservice
- Kubernetes
- Serverless

Coding

- Frontend (NextIS)
- Backend (NodeJS, ExpressJS, Laravel, Go)
- Mobile App (Flutter)

Other

- Cloud VPS (AWS, GCP)
- Linux (Ubuntu, CentOS)
- Docker
- CI/CD